// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Nuvve nuvve",
  options: [
    "Nuvvu nenu",
    "Nuvvu naaku nachav",
    "Nuvve nuvve",
    "Nuvvila"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Race Gurram",
  options: [
    "Gem",
    "Race 2",
    "Galodu",
    "Race Gurram"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Avengers End Game",
  options: [
    "Terminator",
    "The Avengers",
    "Avengers Infinity War",
    "Avengers End Game"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Hello",
  options: [
    "Idharammayilatho",
    "Calling sahasra",
    "Tik Tik Tik",
    "Hello"
  ]
},
   {
  numb: 5,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Love story",
  options: [
    "Style",
    "Love story",
    "Happy days",
    "Natyam"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Oopiri",
  options: [
    "Shyam Singha Roy",
    "Kaashmora",
    "Oopiri",
    "Premam"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Fidha",
  options: [
    "Arya 2",
    "Andhala Rakshasi",
    "Fidha",
    "Rx 100"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Age Of Ultron",
  options: [
    "Terminator",
    "Robots",
    "Thor: Love and Thunder",
    "Age Of Ultron"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Nijam",
  options: [
    "Takkari donga",
    "Jayam",
    "Nijam",
    "Sainikudu"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Kabaddi",
  options: [
    "Krishnashtami ",
    "Kabaddi",
    "Okkadu",
    "Radha"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 11,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Bommarillu",
  options: [
    "Nana",
    "Nannaku Prematho",
    "Bommarillu",
    "S/O Satyamurthy"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 12,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Pelli choopulu",
  options: [
    "Husharu",
    "Pelli choopulu",
    "Taxiwala",
    "Ulavacharu biryani"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 13,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Snehithudu",
  options: [
    "Snehithudu",
    "Rangam",
    "Maharshi",
    "Leader"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 14,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Spyder",
  options: [
    "Ninnu Kori",
    "Mahanati",
    "Spyder",
    "Danger"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 15,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Happy Birthday",
  options: [
    "F3",
    "Happy Deathday",
    "Money money more money ",
    "Happy Birthday"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 16,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Middle class melodies",
  options: [
    "Middle class melodies",
    "Ulavacharu biryani",
    "Premam",
    "MCA"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 17,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Sahasam",
  options: [
    "Golimaar",
    "Sahasam",
    "Souryam",
    "Lakshyam"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 18,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Raja the great",
  options: [
    "Raja the great",
    "Power",
    "Nippu",
    "Touch chesi chudu"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 19,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Ala vaikunthapurramuloo",
  options: [
    "Iddharammayilatho",
    "Badri",
    "Madam",
    "Ala vaikunthapurramuloo"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 20,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Lingaa",
  options: [
    "Bunny",
    "Lingaa",
    "Bagiradha",
    "Sri anjaneyam"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 21,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Vedam",
  options: [
    "Dongodu",
    "Drishyam",
    "Vedam",
    "Dhrona"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 22,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Nuvve kavali",
  options: [
    "Snehitudu",
    "Nuvve kavali",
    "Kerintha",
    "Aanandham"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 23,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Prema katha chitram",
  options: [
    "Deyyam",
    "Aa intlo",
    "Antha:puram",
    "Prema katha chitram"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 24,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Khaidi",
  options: [
    "Khaidi",
    "Kaaki",
    "Bheeshma",
    "Pushpa the rise"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 25,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Mahanati",
  options: [
    "Mahanati",
    "Abhinetri",
    "Khadgam",
    "Ok Bangaram"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 26,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Hit the first case",
  options: [
    "Ghani",
    "Hit the first case",
    "Lakshya",
    "Liger"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 27,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Satyam",
  options: [
    "Katha",
    "Satyam",
    "Premakatha",
    "Shyam singha roy"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 28,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Ninne premistha",
  options: [
    "Gaalipatam",
    "Ninne premistha",
    "Ave kallu",
    "kanupapa"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 29,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Vakeel saab",
  options: [
    "Monagadu",
    "Bheemla nayak",
    "Temper",
    "Vakeel saab"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 30,
  question: " ",
  answer: "F3",
  options: [
    "Paisa vasool",
    "F3",
    "Navvule navvulu",
    "Jaathi ratnalu"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 31,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Devudu chesina manushulu",
  options: [
    "Devudu chesina manushulu",
    "Amar akhbar anthoni",
    "Kick",
    "Khatarnak"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 32,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Shatamanam bhavati",
  options: [
    "Rangde",
    "100% love",
    "Shatamanam bhavati",
    "Fidda"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 33,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Nannaku prematho",
  options: [
    "Nannaku prematho",
    "Butterfly",
    "Shayam singha roy",
    "Manam"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 34,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Gruham",
  options: [
    "Ekkadiki pothavu chinnavada",
    "Gruham",
    "Aa intlo",
    "Dheyam"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 35,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Chalo",
  options: [
    " Chal mohan ranga",
    "Hello",
    "Chalo",
    "Run raja run"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 36,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Kshanam",
  options: [
    "Spy",
    "Agent sai srinivasa athreya",
    "Kshanam",
    "Kanam"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 37,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Dj (Duvvada jagannadham)",
  options: [
    "Dj thillu",
    "Gangstar",
    "Krishnarjuna yuddham",
    "Dj (Duvvada jagannadham)"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 38,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Baahubali-2: The Conclusion",
  options: [
    "Bimbisara",
    "Baahubali-1: The Beginning",
    "Baahubali-2: The Conclusion",
    "Anaganaga o dheerudu"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 39,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Gentleman",
  options: [
    "Gentleman",
    "Ashta chamma",
    "Ala modalaindi",
    "Pilla jamindhar"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 40,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Orey bujjiga",
  options: [
    "Nanna nenu naa boyfriends",
    "Kumari 21F",
    "Orey bujjiga",
    "Eedo rakam aado rakam"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 41,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Yevade subramanyam",
  options: [
    "Keshava",
    "Pelli choopulu",
    "Dwaraka",
    "Yevade subramanyam"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 42,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Bheemla nayak",
  options: [
    "RRR",
    "Bheemla nayak",
    "Jai lava kusa",
    "Nayak"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 43,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Kathanayakudu",
  options: [
    "Kathanayakudu",
    "Krishna",
    "Karthikeya 2",
    "Subramaniapuram"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 44,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Rocketry: The nambi effect",
  options: [
    "Antariksham 9000 KMPH",
    "Rashmi rocket",
    "Rocketry: The nambi effect",
    "Adbhutham"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 45,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Major",
  options: [
    "Major",
    "Sita ramam",
    "Sarileru neekevvaru",
    "The Ghazi attack"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 46,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Colour photo",
  options: [
    "Pushpa:The rise",
    "Colour photo",
    "Endukante premanta",
    "Ready"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 47,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Radhe shyam",
  options: [
    "Kgf Chapter2",
    "Titanic",
    "Radhe shyam",
    "Gangotri"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 48,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Nee sneham",
  options: [
    "Nee sneham",
    "Vunnadhi okate zindagi",
    "Sye",
    "Snehamante idera"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 49,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Raja raja chora",
  options: [
    "Swami ra ra",
    "Chanti",
    "Hit",
    "Raja raja chora"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 50,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Malleswari",
  options: [
    "Cinderella",
    "Malleswari",
    "Queen",
    "Sita ramam"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 51,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Manmadhudu-2",
  options: [
    "Premam",
    "Manmadhudu-2",
    "Raju gari gadhi-2",
    "Majili"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 52,
  question: " ",
  answer: "SwamyRara",
  options: [
    "SwamyRara",
    "ChorBazaar",
    "Raja Raja Chora",
    "Dongata"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 53,
  question: " ",
  answer: "Virata Parvam",
  options: [
    "Virapan",
    "narapa",
    "Dhandupalem",
    "Virata Parvam"
  ]
},
];
